seowebhosting.net 2014-12-21

# Privacy Policy - SEO Web Hosting

**We're committed to ensuring that we respect and protect our customers' privacy.**

Privacy is extremely important at SEO Web Hosting and we are committed to ensuring that we respect and protect our customers' privacy. The three basic tenets of our privacy policies here at SEO Web Hosting are:

  * **Collect only what we need.** We will not ask you for information we do not need to serve you in some way. Our job is to be your web hosting company, not to be a data mining company.
  * **Share only when we have to.** We do not and will not share any of your personal information unless we have your permission or we are required to do so by law or similar process.
  * **Ensure that we keep private information private.** We will do what we can (within reason, of course) to ensure that any personal information you have given us will remains private.

The three tenets above are intentionally very simple. If you are interested in more details regarding our privacy policies, keep reading. If you have any questions, feel free to get in touch with us. We are available 24/7. 

### SEO Web Hosting Privacy Policy

SEO Web Hosting ("SEO Web Hosting") provides a variety of web hosting products and related services to its international customer base. It is our policy to respect and protect our customers' privacy. This privacy policy begins applying to visitors and customers as soon as they visit SEO Web Hosting's website for the first time.

### Website Visitors

Like most website operators, SEO Web Hosting collects non-personally-identifying information of the sort that web browsers and servers typically make available, such as the browser type, language preference, referring site, and the date and time of each visitor request. SEO Web Hosting's purpose in collecting non-personally identifying information is to better understand how SEO Web Hosting's visitors use its website. From time to time, SEO Web Hosting may release non-personally-identifying information in the aggregate. e.g., by publishing a report on trends in the usage of its website.

### Gathering of Personally-Identifying Information

Certain visitors to SEO Web Hosting's website choose to interact with SEO Web Hosting in ways that require SEO Web Hosting to gather personally-identifying information. The amount and type of information that SEO Web Hosting gathers depends on the nature of the interaction. For example, we ask visitors who choose to signup for our newsletter for their name and email address. Those who engage in transactions with SEO Web Hosting, usually by purchasing web hosting services or registering a domain name, for example, are asked to provide additional information, including as necessary the personal and financial information required to process those transactions. In each case, SEO Web Hosting collects such information only insofar as is necessary or appropriate to fulfill the purpose of the visitor's interaction with SEO Web Hosting. SEO Web Hosting does not disclose personally-identifying information other than as described below. And visitors can always refuse to supply personally-identifying information, with the caveat that it may prevent them from engaging in certain website-related activities, including from becoming a customer of SEO Web Hosting.

In some cases, SEO Web Hosting will ask website visitors wishing to become customers of SEO Web Hosting to provide additional information beyond what was requested in the signup form. This information is requested to verify the customer's identity and to reduce the likelihood of fraud, which is common in the web hosting industry in which SEO Web Hosting operates. Customers not wishing to provide such information as requested may not be permitted to become customers of SEO Web Hosting.

### Aggregated Statistics

SEO Web Hosting may collect statistics about the behavior of visitors to its websites and its customers. For instance, SEO Web Hosting may publish the number of emails sent per month or the total number of installations of a certain software package. SEO Web Hosting may display this information publicly or provide it to others. However, SEO Web Hosting does not disclose personally-identifying information other than as described below.

### Protection of Certain Personally-Identifying Information

SEO Web Hosting discloses potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only to those of its employees, contractors and affiliated organizations that (i) need to know that information in order to process it on SEO Web Hosting's behalf or to provide services available to SEO Web Hosting's customers, and (ii) that have agreed not to disclose it to others. Some of those employees, contractors and affiliated organizations may be located outside of your home country; by using SEO Web Hosting's products and services, you consent to the transfer of such information to them. SEO Web Hosting will not rent or sell potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information to anyone. Other than to its employees, contractors and affiliated organizations, as described above, SEO Web Hosting discloses potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only in response to a subpoena, court order or other governmental request.

If you are a customer of SEO Web Hosting and have supplied your email address, SEO Web Hosting may occasionally send you an email to tell you about new products or services, solicit your feedback, inform you of an outage or interruption in service, or just keep you up to date with what's going on with SEO Web Hosting and our products and services. We primarily use our blog, forums, Twitter account, and similar presences to communicate this type of information, so we expect to keep this type of email to a minimum. If you send us a request (for example via a support email or through our billing system), we reserve the right to publish it (with personally identifiable information removed as necessary) in order to help us clarify or respond to your request or to help us support other customers. SEO Web Hosting takes all measures reasonably necessary to protect against the unauthorized access, use, alteration or destruction of potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information.

### Cookies

A cookie is a string of information that a website stores on a visitor's computer, and that the visitor's browser provides to the website each time the visitor returns. SEO Web Hosting uses cookies to help SEO Web Hosting identify and track visitors, their usage of SEO Web Hosting's website, and their website access preferences. SEO Web Hosting visitors who do not wish to have cookies placed on their computers should set their browsers to refuse cookies before using SEO Web Hosting's website or using its products or services, with the drawback that certain features of SEO Web Hosting's websites, products, and services may not function properly without the aid of cookies.

### Privacy Policy Changes

Although most changes are likely to be minor, SEO Web Hosting may change its Privacy Policy from time to time, with or without notice, and in SEO Web Hosting's sole discretion. SEO Web Hosting will post changes to its Privacy Policy directly on this page and encourages visitors to regularly check this page for any changes to this Privacy Policy. Your continued use of SEO Web Hosting's products and services after any change in this Privacy Policy will constitute your acceptance of such change.
